I'm the most patient
Like I walk out of hospitals
I'm the most focused
Like I'm a 5D Canon
Cause I blast off
Shoot off onto my vision
Combination of my strategy and my natural intuition
Look around town I'm the most underrated
Consultant, Forbes writer
And I'm Georgetown graduated
Middle Eastern in general
in specific جداوي
Come and across my territory
Look at how we live it
Cause بين هذي ودي
أنا مواطن سعودي
أفتخر بجميع أولاد وبنات حدودي
بكل شخص أهدى حياته يحمي حدودي
أفتخر بأصولي
من شمالي لجنوبي
I owe a lot
To this country and it's leadership team
United we stand together
Our nation's a team
من أهل مكة والمدينة
للرياض والقصيم
من أهل جدة وجيزان
لتبوك وعسير
كلنا سند
لبعضنا وللوطن
نبني نعمر أرضنا
ونرفع فينا الأمل
مشوارنا فبدايته
وحنسابق الزمن
نسعى نحقق حلمنا
مهما كان الثمن
Vision 2030
My country is building up
All my people making history
We're never giving up
We're full of hope and ambition
Every morning we rise
Bringing change and we see it
Right in front of our eyes
Movie theatres are up now
Women can drive
We do it at our own pace
Move at our own time
And it's time we show the world
How we do it up in Saudi
Where the sun shines all day
Never cloudy
Never doubt me
I'm stating the truth
This country's future lies on the shoulders of youth
هذه رسالة خاصة
لجيلنا المثابر
بلادنا في أيدينا
نبني فيها فلنعاصر
لا تسأل ماذا بلدك ستعطيك
اسأل ماذا اعطيت وكيف تعطي من مزيد
فيد ستستفيد
أحمِد ربك المجيد
بلادنا بخير
يجعل كل يوم عيد
I’m not saying we’ve made it past the finish line
All I’m saying is we’re on our way
And on our way I know we’re going through
A lot of changes
Through a lot of struggles and challenges
And it's not easy
It’s going to get harder before it gets easier
But I know that down the road
We'll look back at this time
In our lives
And be proud of the work that we did
It's all for the best
وشكر خاص لكل شاب وشابة
رجل وإمرأة
ساهموا في تطوير بلدنا
التغير والنهضة تبدأ منكم
من الشعب
في المدارس
في الجامعات
في القطاع الحكومي
في القطاع الخاص
الطريق طويل
لاكن احنا شعب مثابر
مستمرين
اليوم
وكل يوم
كلنا سند
لبعضنا وللوطن
نبني نعمر أرضنا
ونرفع فينا الأمل
مشوارنا فبدايته
وحنسابق الزمن
نسعى نحقق حلمنا
مهما كان الثمن